Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
Cultural Festival
Welcome to
#08  Cultural Festival II
Here you go.
This way!
Accurate
Wow! He got it right!
Cultural Festival Venue
The library is
open as a
rest area.
-Library Committee
The library is
open as a
rest area.
-Library Committee
Did you see the movie
everyone's talking about?
The one based on a fairy tale?
The live-action adaptation? Not yet.
Was it good?
Yeah.
It looked gorgeous, and the
dresses were beautiful, too.
You're really girly, huh?
Not what I'd have expected.
It's not like I have particularly
girlish tastes.
Nekozaki
Where are you?
Got a favor to ask. Would you
mind?
It's no use, though.
Girls who just wait around aren't
exactly en vogue right now.
Huh? A lot of people go to see
movies like that, though.
Maybe because that's how
they wish things could be.
That someday their prince on a white
horse will come, and they'll be happy.
Is that really how it is?
Wait, Kamiya-san, did seeing that movie make
you want to ask me about Shikimori-san?
Maybe.
You were so intense about it.
I wondered what was up.
Kamiya-san.
"Anything important to you should be kept
within your heart and not shared,"
or so they say.
Or so who says?
The girl in the movie whose
love wasn't realized.
I-I see...
I never thought I'd have this
conversation with you, though.
Is it weird? Does it not suit me?
Or it just... isn't like me?
No, I'm enjoying it.
I'm glad, then.
Kamiya? You here?
There you are.
Nekozaki-san? What brings you here?
Oh, you know...
I need to borrow Kamiya.
Cultural Festival Venue
The library is
open as a
rest area.
-Library Committee
The library is
open as a
rest area.
-Library Committee
I'm sorry! If it's not too much trouble,
would you please trade numbers with me?
Huh? Uh...
You're Shikimori-san... right?
What's this about, Nekozaki?
You know the Couple Numbers game, right?
She wants to trade her number for yours.
Why my number?
W-Well...
Because you have the same
number as the person I like.
Cultural Festival Venue
The library is
open as a
rest area.
-Library Committee
The library is
open as a
rest area.
-Library Committee
In that case, sure.
Really?!
See? I told you!
Kamiya's not interested in this
kinda thing, so it's fine!
Thank you so much!
It's hot in the hallway.
Why don't you talk in here?
Wait, Shikimori-san?!
I-I came to get you because I figured
your shift would be over soon!
O-Oh, really?
What were they talking about?
It's okay. You can go.
I'll handle the last twenty minutes—
I can't!
I can't force you to do
the work by yourself!
Okay... You're rather diligent, huh?
Micchon, have a seat and wait in here,
where it's nice and cool.
S-Sure.
Hachimitsu should have come with us.
Thanks for being so considerate, Kamiya-san.
That shy, little dork!
Thanks for everything today, Kamiya-san.
I'm glad we had the chance to talk so much.
See ya.
Yeah, later.
Café
Sorry I'm late.
Kamiya-san!
Kamiya! We've been waiting for you!
Now we can make up for lost time!
Kamiya! Took you long enough!
With Kamiya-san here,
our profits will soar!
All right! Let's do this!
Who is she? She's so pretty!
And so tall! She looks like a model!
Nice!
Wanna try talking to her?
No way.
Apparently, she's single.
For real?! I'm going for it, then!
Thank you for waiting.
Kamiya!
Come here a sec!
Please enjoy.
We get tons more customers
when she's here.
Should we just have her stand by the door?
Hey, looks like we could talk to her now!
Don't bother. She won't
give you the time of day.
She has a great figure.
I bet she'd look good in anything.
Maybe she's not interested in other people?
Hey, let's ask for another
picture with her!
She just seems way out of reach.
I wonder what she's into.
Maybe she's fine with just standing there.
I wanna talk to her!
Nah, I bet there's a chance!
She looks super athletic.
I wonder why she's just standing there.
Wanna try asking for her name?
Why don't you try just saying hi?
I wonder if she'd come up in a search...
Kamiya?
Something wrong?
Sorry... I need to step out for a bit.
Man, I never would've thought
she'd show up herself.
But she seemed like a nice, honest girl.
Nothing like me.
I need to just throw these
feelings away already.
Kamiya-san.
Did you need something?
I came to return this.
I felt like I was being unfair.
Everyone swaps numbers.
I don't think there's
anything unfair about it.
That's not what I mean.
This is something I can't take from you.
Isn't that right, Kamiya-san?
Why...
Kamiya-san, you're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm okay.
You're the one who got hurt, aren't you?
Why'd the bookshelf suddenly fall over?
Sorry, Kamiya-san.
This was my fault.
You shouldn't have to help me.
It was just a fluke.
It's not your fault.
You really are nice, Kamiya-san.
Am I?
I get a lot of "she acts so cool" and
"I can't guess what she's thinking," but...
Really?
You are nice.
Why...
I think I'm the only one
who's figured it out,
but the way you acted earlier...
And why did that make you
want to return this to me?
You didn't come to tell me not
to ever go near him again?
No. I just didn't want to
do anything rude to you.
Because I don't think anyone who
likes the person I like can be bad.
If you really felt nothing at all when
you gave it to me, that's fine.
But...
if I made you lie and caused you
pain, that's unfair to you.
Are you sure?
Isn't this basically helping your enemy?
I'm sure.
Izumi-san would probably do the same.
Yeah... I can definitely see that.
Shikimori-san...
Yes?
I don't need that after all.
Huh?
What I had was just a piece of paper.
But...
You don't need to worry so much about it.
I have no intention of ever
telling him how I feel.
I never intended for anyone to ever find out.
I guess I wronged you, huh?
I didn't mean to make you
feel bad or anything.
Sorry about that.
Sorry...
Library
Sorry I couldn't immediately throw it away.
I won't ever come near him again.
Huh? What is this?
I don't understand it, either.
His quiet kindness made me feel more
comfortable around him than anyone else.
That's all it was.
He thinks of me as a friend,
and I'm betraying him.
Even though he has you...
Why couldn't we have just become friends?
Let's stop this now.
I'm sorry. I never meant to hurt you.
You don't need to apologize to me,
and I can't make up your mind for you.
I don't know anything about you,
but there is one thing I know.
You're trying to sacrifice your feelings,
for Izumi-san and me.
I don't care if you think
I'm acting high-and-mighty.
It still makes me happy
that you're such a kind person.
So you should cherish
those feelings you have.
Sorry. I'm okay now.
Anyway, shouldn't you
get back to Izumi-kun?
He's probably gonna start
crying any time now.
Oh, right!
Shikimori-san...
See ya.
Yeah! See you later!
Jeez... How long has it been since
I last cried in front of someone?
She really is something, though,
letting someone like me
cry on her shoulder...
I'm so glad she's his girlfriend.
I hope they'll be happy.
It's the last day of the festival.
And today is...
exactly one year since we started dating,
and Shikimori-san's birthday!
I found that out too late to
congratulate her last year...
My birthday? It was last month.
What?!
So this year I went shopping in advance...
U-U-U-Um, I want to give
my g-girlfriend a gift...
C-Can you recommend anyfing?
Hearts are always popular
for things like that.
This year, I'm giving her a gift!
I'm off!
Oh, you're leaving early today.
I left early the past two days, too!
Did you?
Animal Café
Check out our animal café!
Quit pushing! I said stop!
Accurate
Wow! He's right again!
That's crazy! How's he doing it?!
Okonomiyaki
Monjayaki
All right, so...
Great work over these past
three festival days!
Cheers!
Tears!
Ranked 8th
in Festival Profits
I can tell you two are bummed about losing.
If we'd ranked first in profits,
we would've gotten free after-party tickets!
So now we're paying for this
out of our own pockets!
I hope Izumi-san will be okay...
The free food I was dreaming of...
Can those two get drunk on juice?
Which class ended up coming in first?
Oh... Apparently, the third-year class with
the fortune-telling booth won by a mile.
Huh...
I guess the third-years
really did go all-out.
Here.
I thought we were doing pretty good...
Hey, show me your Couple Numbers photo.
You swapped numbers, right?
Uh...
W-We didn't take one.
What?!
When did you show up, Nekozaki?
Who cares?! Explain, Micchon!
Uh, well...
I lost it.
What?! C'mon, you're not Izumi!
What about me?
I got careless.
Aw, man!
I'm gonna call you Ditzymori.
We'll get first place next year!
See ya!
See you next week!
Bye-bye!
Shikimori-san...
Yes?
Do you still have some time?
Want to go to the park?
S-Sure, that's fine...
Wh-What did you want to talk about?
W-Well... um...
Happy birthday!
A-Also... it's our first
anniversary, kinda?
They ended up being the same gift...
I don't know much about accessories and
stuff, so I don't know if you'll like it...
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy!
I'm glad you seem to feel better.
Huh?
You've been acting a bit off since you came
back from whatever you had to do yesterday.
I wondered if something happened.
No, nothing happened.
Can I open this now?
Sure.
Oh, how cute!
I'll put it on for you.
Huh?!
Let me see.
O-Okay...
Shikimori-san...
No matter what happens,
I'm always on your side, okay?
You never change, Izumi-san.
Really?
A friend just told me the
other day that I've changed.
I'm sure that's just because your good parts
are showing through more.
Everyone's starting to see them.
And I... I should be happy
about that, but...
I don't know why...
but it bothers me a bit.
What if you end up drifting
far away from me?
What am I even talking about, right?
Please don't ever change.
Stay the way you are.
You don't trust me?
Of course I do!
But... But...
You say I haven't changed,
but I think I've changed.
A year ago, you changed me.
But it's not enough yet.
If the way I am now makes you
worry, I'll get stronger.
I can't be as cool as you,
but I do want to get stronger.
I want to put your mind at ease
so you'll trust me as much as I trust you,
and so you can relax and
smile when you're with me.
Shikimori-san?
I want the same thing...
You're crying?!
You're already not smiling!
...s-same... same thing...
What'd you say?!
Sob
This is the first time I've seen you cry!
You don't need to offer your opinions!
Anyway, please stop crying.
I've made up my mind.
About what?
No matter what kind of sweet, pretty,
alluring girl may come along...
I'm never going to let you go.
O-Okay...
Oh! I-It's really late.
We should head home.
Wait!
Does it look nice on me?
Yeah.
My girlfriend is super cute.
SEE YOU~